Open the PT Activity. Perform the tasks in the activity instructions and then answer the question.
Fill in the blank. Do not use abbreviations.
Which command is missing on the Layer 3 switch to restore the full connectivity between PC1 and the web server?
	ip address 192.168.20.1 255.255.255.0

Refer to the exhibit. The switch does the routing for the hosts that connect to VLAN 5. If the PC accesses a web server from the Internet, at what point will a VLAN number be added to the frame?
	No VLAN number is added to the frame in this design.

What is a disadvantage of using router-on-a-stick inter-VLAN routing?
	does not scale well beyond 50 VLANs

Inter-VLAN communication is not occurring in a particular building of a school. Which two commands could the network administrator use to verify that inter-VLAN communication was working properly between a router and a Layer 2 switch when the router-on-a-stick design method is implemented? (Choose two.)
	From the router, issue the show ip route command.
	From the switch, issue the show interface trunk command.

Which statement describes a disadvantage of using router subinterfaces for inter-VLAN routing?
	Routed traffic must contend for bandwidth on a single router interface.

Refer to the exhibit. Which command can the administrator issue to change the VLAN10 status to up?​
	Switch1(config)# vlan 10

Refer to the exhibit. A network administrator is verifying the configuration of inter-VLAN routing. Users complain that PCs on different VLANs cannot communicate. Based on the output, what are two configuration errors on switch interface Gi1/1? (Choose two.)
	Gi1/1 is configured as trunk mode.
	Gi1/1 is in the default VLAN.

Refer to the exhibit. A router-on-a-stick configuration was implemented for VLANs 15, 30, and 45, according to the show running-config command output. PCs on VLAN 45 that are using the 172.16.45.0 /24 network are having trouble connecting to PCs on VLAN 30 in the 172.16.30.0 /24 network. Which error is most likely causing this problem?​
	There is an incorrect IP address configured on GigabitEthernet 0/0.30